So nice to meet you.
(Mrs Cooper:)Nice to meet you, too.
How was your flight?
(Dr Hofstadter:)Very pleasant. And yours?
(Mrs Cooper:)Lovely. Almost
as if someone--
(Mrs Cooper:)not saying who-- was
watching over the plane.
(Dr Hofstadter:)You're kidding, right?
(Leonard:)Subtle, Mom,
real subtle.
(Bernadette:)Stuart.
(Leonard:)Morning.
(Bernadette:)We talked about this.
(Bernadette:)I don't mind you
still living here,
(Bernadette:)but we got to have
some rules.
(Bernadette:)And rule number one is pants.
Hey, hey.
(clears throat)
(Mrs Cooper:)You must be very
proud of your son.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Oh, yes.
(Dr Hofstadter:)He recently argued a case
before the Supreme Court.
(Mrs Cooper:)He did?
(Dr Hofstadter:)Oh, you mean this son.